## ♣ ABOUT ME

I have been working in IT for 10 years, I an getting specialized in Java development to enhance my working base and progress within the industry.

I am a Team player always striving to develop personally and professionally by accepting every new challenge, networking with other industry professionals and consistently placing client solutions, satisfaction and service at the forefront of operations.

- xavier.lamourec@gmail.com
- +353 83 88 46 758
- https://github.com/xbreizh

#### https://xbreizh.github.io/xavier-lamourec

w

**JAVA** 

Spring ...

Struts .

Hibernate . .

Web Services ■ ■ ■

Junit - Mockito

Git • •

Jenkins •••

SonarQube ...

■ DATABASE

Oracle / postgreSql • • •

FRONT-END

html / css / javascript • • •

# XAVIER LAMOUREC JAVA DEVELOPER

https://xbreizh.github.io/xavier-lamourec



## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### TECHNICAL SUPPORT SPECIALIST

**≝** Smartfocus

**i** 2017 – 2019

#### **RESPONSIBILITIES**

**UI Support / Training** 

Data Support: Database management / basic shell and SQL scripts API Support: Assisting clients with company API usage (REST/SOAP)

#### TECHNICAL SUPPORT ANALYST

**I** Smartfocus

**2013 – 2017** 

#### RESPONSIBILITIES

Technical assistance for a complex emailing platform CSS / Html / Email campaign creation / Segment / Report

#### SUPPORT DESK AGENT

**≣** Accenture

**2012 - 2013** 

#### **RESPONSIBILITIES**

Technical assistance for company workers

#### LEVEL 2 - SERVICE DESK AGENT

**En CPL company; Hewlett Packard Client** 

**2010 – 2012** 

#### **RESPONSIBILITIES**

Resolving complex technical issues and handling escalations and complaints

Mentored new staff / outage management

Worked across various technologies: Windows Servers; Active Directory,



## **EDUCATION**

### JAVA DEVELOPER PATH TRAINING

Open Classrooms, Academy of Paris

📋 2018 - Current

DESIGN PATTERNS, STRUTS, SPRING, HIBERNATE, GIT, DOCKER, JENKINS, SONARQUBE, JAXWS, SQL, JAVASCRIPT (GITHUB)

#### MASTER OF SCIENCES (STAPS)

in University of Corsica

**i** 2007



## **LANGUAGES**

FRENCH

ENGLISH

ROMANIAN

SPANISH